Guide to the Amos Vogel Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Writings, 1896-1996
  - Subseries III.4: Short Stories, 1960-1985
    - "Fields of Rain," 1980-1981 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - "Great Teacher," 1980 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - "The Hamburger Hold-Hp," 1963 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - "How Lori Washed Skyscraper Windows," 1963 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - "In the Loetschental," 1985 July (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Master List of Short Stories, 1962-1983 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - "Memory and Prevention," 1983 April (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Outline for a Film Concerning God, 1970 May (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - "Philosophy in the Surf," 1966 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - "The Pointer Moves," 1968 March (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - "The Power of Books," 1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - "Singing Regardless of Weather," 1982 April 18 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - "Tears," 1981 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - "Tremors of Recognition," 1971 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - "Willie and the Six Hour Flu," 1968 March (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.5: Articles and Essays, 1958-1996
    The last subseries consists primarily of articles and essays that Amos Vogel regularly contributed to such well-known publications as Film Comment, Evergreen, The New York Times, and The Village Voice. Within these texts, Vogel addressed the then-current film culture, including the issues faced by avant-garde directors, and the future of the independent (and mainstream) film industry. He also reviewed films that he had screened at various festivals that had stood out in some way. Also held in this subseries are letters sent to editors, program notes for film festivals, in particular the New York Film Festival, which he founded, and book reviews.
    - Evergreen
      - Brussels, 1958 November-December (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - "The Day Rap Brown Became a Press Agent for Paramount," 1969 June (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - "Money Crunch," 1981 September-October (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - "Thirteen Confusions," 1967 June (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Two Book Reviews, 1970 January-April (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Film Comment
      - All Columns, 1974-1983 (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - Alternative Cinema Conference, 1979 November-December (Box 129, Folder 15)
      - American Film Festival, 1979 September-October (Box 129, Folder 16)
      - "Amos Vogel and Bruce Connor: Two Views of the Money Crunch," 1981 September-October (Box 129, Folder 17)
      - "Amos Vogel on Documentary Films," 1974 September-October (Box 129, Folder 18)
      - Animation and Computer, 1974 July-August (Box 129, Folder 19)
      - "The Atom and Eve of Destruction," 1983 February (Box 129, Folder 20)
      - "Autumn in New York," 1977 November-December (Box 129, Folder 21)
      - "Avant-Garde at the American Film Festival," 1980 July-August (Box 129, Folder 22)
      - "The Avant-Garde of the Seventies," 1975 May-June (Box 129, Folder 23)
      - Berlin's Forum," 1981 July-August (Box 129, Folder 24)
      - Cannes, 1978 1978 September-October (Box 129, Folder 25)
      - "Choosing and Cruising," 1980 January-February (Box 129, Folder 26)
      - Deal, 1978 November-December (Box 129, Folder 27)
      - "Eternal Experimenter," 1985 February (Box 129, Folder 28)
      - Ethnological Cinema, 1978 July-August (Box 129, Folder 29)
      - Ethnological Revelations, 1975 November-December (Box 129, Folder 30)
      - "Film Funding," 1978 March-April (Box 129, Folder 31)
      - The Flaherty Myth, 1979 March-April (Box 129, Folder 32)
      - "Grim Death," 1980 March-April (Box 129, Folder 33)
      - "Hallo Berlin," 1988 May-June (Box 129, Folder 34)
      - "Herzog in Berlin," 1977 September-October (Box 129, Folder 35)
      - "Hints to the Wise," 1977 March-April (Box 129, Folder 36)
      - "Lessons in Darkness," 1992 May (Box 129, Folder 37)
      - Mehrjui's The Cycle, 1979 May-June (Box 129, Folder 38)
      - "Missionary Positions," 1982 May-June (Box 129, Folder 39)
      - "More Apocalypse Now," 1983 June (Box 129, Folder 40)
      - New Modernist Film Magazines, 1979 January-February (Box 129, Folder 41)
      - "Nods and Ends," 1980 September-October (Box 129, Folder 42)
      - Northwest Film Festival Winners, 1980 November-December (Box 129, Folder 43)
      - "On Seeing A Mirage," 1981 January-February (Box 129, Folder 44)
      - "Paradoxes and Dreams: The Independents in Berlin," 1988 March (Box 129, Folder 45)
      - "Parker Tyler," 1974 November-December (Box 129, Folder 46)
      - “Programmer’s Notes,” 1976 May-June (Box 129, Folder 47)
      - “Reader’s Digest Version of Avant-Garde Film History II,” 1976 September-October (Box 129, Folder 48)
      - “Reader’s Digest Version of Avant-Garde Film History III,” 1976 November-December (Box 129, Folder 49)
      - “Reader’s Digest Version of Avant-Garde Film History IV,” 1977 January-February (Box 129, Folder 50)
      - Recent Political Films, 1978 January-February (Box 129, Folder 51)
      - Reply to Amos Vogel Series, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 52)
      - “Smashing Myths about the Information Industry,” 1982 November-December (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - “Smiles and Tears (I-II),” 1976 January-1978 April (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Sokurov Article, 1989 June (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - “Stalking Asparagus,” 1981 May-June (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - “Structuralism” 1982 January-February (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - “The Structuralist Incursion: The Setting,” 1975 July-August (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - “The Structuralist Incurstion: The Literature,” 1975 September-October (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - “Structures,” 1975 January-February (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - “Subversive Mysteries (I-II),” 1977 May-August (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - “Three Iconoclast Originals,” 1987 March-June (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - “Toward the Self,” 1975 March-April (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - Untitled, 1974 May-June (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - “The Vital Statistics of Media Centers,” 1979 July-August (Box 130, Folder 13)
      - “Works of Despair,” 1983 August (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Film Culture
      - Experimental Film Symposium, 1957 (Box 130, Folder 15)
      - “Love in a City,” 1957 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - “‘I Make Films to Exorcise My Fears’: A Talk with Bernardo Bertolucci,” 1970 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Letters to the Editor
      - Bad Michael Wood Article, 1984/1985 (Box 130, Folder 18)
      - Race Discrimination, 1978 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - The New York Times
      - “Avante-Garde Film Festive: Nudity and Contemplation,” 1968 January 21 (Box 130, Folder 20)
      - “Can We Not Forget the Evil She Did?” 1973 May 13 (Box 130, Folder 21)
      - “The Censor Always Loses,” 1968 September 15 (Box 130, Folder 22)
      - Letters to the Editor, 1990-1994 (Box 130, Folder 23)
      - Mini, 1970 (Box 130, Folder 24)
      - The New York Film Festival
        - “The New Cinema,” undated, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 25)
        - “Witness and Catalyst,” 1965 September (Box 130, Folder 26)
        - “Unfilled Promise,” 1983 (Box 130, Folder 27)
      - Oberhausen Film Festival, 1964 February 16 (Box 130, Folder 28)
      - “Onus Is Not on the Artist: It Is We Who Must Learn,” 1966 September 11 (Box 130, Folder 29)
      - Untitled Article, 1965 (Box 130, Folder 30)
    - Other Journals
      - “Advice to Moviegoers,” 1968 September (Box 130, Folder 31)
      - Art in the Third Reich, 1982 (Box 130, Folder 32)
      - Austrian Cultural Institute, 1994 (Box 130, Folder 33)
      - Berlin Diary: “Two Weeks in November,” 1990 Spring (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - “Blood-Stained Works: The Glasnost Film Festival,” 1989 June (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - “The Camera as Pen,” 1966-1967 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Cinema 16, 1950s, (3 Folders) (Box 131, Folder 4 to 6)
      - Defining Independent Film, 1983 March (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Democracy: Manipulations and Possibilities,” 1969 July (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Exit Hollywood/Viennale, 1993-1996 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - "The Exorcist," 1974 July (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - “Film as Art,” 1975 (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - “Films that Tread on Toes,” 1965 March (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - “Flares in the Night,” 1969 December (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - Free Associations, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - Independent American Film, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - John Kennedy, 1992 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      - Leo Dratfield, 1987 March (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - “The Little Foxes and the Big Mink,” 1977 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - New York Film Festival 20th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Oberhausen, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Olympia Article, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - “Notes for a Film Festival,” 1969-1970 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - [Pantomime?] in [Russian Film], undated (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Prague Article, 1970s (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Raiders of the Lost Ark, 1982-1983 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - “Risks and Rewards of Cinematic Clairvoyance,” 1965 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - “The Shape of Flames Forty Years After,” 1979 July (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Summerhill School, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Sweet Movie, 1975 October (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - “Towards a New Cinema,” 1958-1966, (3 Folders) (Box 132, Folder 14 to 16)
      - “The Year Cannes Turned Marxist-Leninist,” 1980 Winter (Box 132, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous Articles, 1965-1979, 1992-1994 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Program Notes
      - “Film as Art,” 1979 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - “Film as Art,” 1980 (Box 132, Folder 20)
      - New York Film Festival, 1963-1968 (Box 132, Folder 21)
      - “Whispering Pages,” 1994 March (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Village Voice
      - “Atrocities and Artless Innocence,” 1972 February 3 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - “The Bad and the Beautiful: La Guerre Est Commence,” 1968 May (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - “Brakhage, Brecht, Berlin, Eden West & East,” 1965 December 23 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - “Bugs Bunny and the Computers,” 1974 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - "Cannes 1971: Blood, Violence, and Sex," 1971 May-June (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - "Cannes 1971: The Barometers of Pain," 1971 June (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - "Cannes 1972: Evangelism and Encounter Groups," 1972 June 15 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - "Cannes 1972: When Critics Exchange Secret Glances," 1972 June 22 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - "Cannes 1972: Will Film Survive until 2001?" 1972 June 8 (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - "Cuba: Fusing Politics and the Poetic," 1974 July (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - "Each Man for Himself and God Against All," 1972 May 1 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - "Even Dwarfs Started Small," 1972 (Box 133, Folder 13)
      - Flaming Creatures Article, 1964 May 7 (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - "The Humanists of Prague: The Young Czech Cinema," 1967 June 15 (Box 133, Folder 15)
      - "In Paradise Man Is Born Dead," 1971 November (Box 133, Folder 16)
      - "I Made a Glass Hammer," 1971 June (Box 133, Folder 17)
      - "A Mirror of Today's Disaster," 1971 February (Box 133, Folder 18)
      - "Muehl: Up to His Neck in it," 1973 May (Box 133, Folder 19)
      - "The Movie Gap: A Cultural Scandal," 1970 March (Box 133, Folder 20)
      - " A Nation Comes Out of Shell-Shock," 1972 May 4 (Box 133, Folder 21)
      - New Animation at the Whitney, 1972 March 1 (Box 133, Folder 22)
      - "Noshing Under the Knife," 1973 August 2 (Box 133, Folder 23)
      - "One Festival Plus One," 1970 July 9 (Box 133, Folder 24)
      - "'Outrageous Films' at the Whitney," 1973-1974 (Box 133, Folder 25)
      - Parker Tyler, 1974 August 1 (Box 133, Folder 26)
      - "A Poem of Revolt," 1971 March 4 (Box 133, Folder 27)
      - Political Advertisement, 1969 (Box 133, Folder 28)
      - "Reality Through Deformation," 1971 April (Box 133, Folder 29)
      - Siddharta, 1973 August (Box 133, Folder 30)
      - Saturday Morning, 1971 April 30 (Box 133, Folder 31)
      - "Sweet Fireworks," 1971 March (Box 133, Folder 32)
      - "Thank You, Nikita Sergeyevich," 1961 September 21 (Box 133, Folder 33)
      - "Two Little Men Open the Cosmos," 1970s (Box 133, Folder 34)
      - United States Independent Film Roundup, 1972 June 10 (Box 133, Folder 35)
- Series IV: Photographs, 1920-1999
  Series IV is composed of photographs, both professional and nonprofessional, contact sheets, and negatives. There are also slides that Amos Vogel used in to conduct his film lectures. Subjects of these images vary from individuals, such as famous directors and actors, events, for example the Cannes Film Festival and the New York Film Festival, and stills from films themselves. This series is divided into two subseries: General and Film Stills.
  - Subseries IV.1: General, 1927-1999
    Photographs, contact sheets, and negatives held in this subseries are more general in nature. Images in regards to Cinema 16 events and numerous film festivals are held here. Individuals include prominent filmmakers, such as Werner Herzog, Alfred Hitchcock and the Maysles, as well as individuals known as much for their screen time as their behind-the-camera work, for example Charlie Chaplin and Jack Nicholson. There are also photographs from certain Cinema 16 events, for example the "Poetry and the Film" Symposium that featured photographs of writers such as Dylan Thomas and Arthur Miller. Also of interest are photographs from the 1968 filmmakers strike at Cannes in which Jean-Luc Godard, Luis Malle, François Truffaut, Roman Polanski, and other major directors pulled out their films in solidarity with the student and labor uprisings occurring all over the country. Photographs listed under Vogel's VIP term include notable individuals such as John and Yoko Lennon, Salvador Dali, and Alfred Hitchcock.
    - American Avant-garde Filmmakers in Berlin, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 36)
    - Cannes Film Festival, 1968 (Box 133, Folder 37)
    - Cinema 16
      - Audiences, 1948-1955 (Box 133, Folder 38)
      - "An Evening with Fred Zinneman," 1950s (Box 133, Folder 39)
      - "Poetry and the Film," 1953 October 28 (Box 133, Folder 40)
      - Stanley Kramer Event, 1954-1955 (Box 133, Folder 41)
    - Creative Film Foundation Awards
      - General, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Dali, Salvador, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Williams, Tennessee, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Directors, undated, 1970s (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Holland, Robin--Cinema 16 Celebration (Film Forum), 1968 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Individuals
      - Anger, Kenneth, 1947, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Antonioni, Michaelangelo, 1959 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Arrabal, Fernando, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Beeson, Constance, undated (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Bergman, Ingmar, undated (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Bertolucci, Bernardo, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Borowczyk, Walerian, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Brakhage, Stan, undated (Box 134, Folder 13)
      - Bresson, George, undated (Box 134, Folder 14)
      - Broughton, James, 1960s (Box 134, Folder 15)
      - Buñuel, Luis, undated, 1953 (Box 134, Folder 16)
      - Chaplain, Charlie, 1910s, 1970s (Box 134, Folder 17)
      - Clarke, Shirley, undated (Box 134, Folder 18)
      - Clouzot, Henri-Georges, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 19)
      - Cocteau, Jean, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 20)
      - Connor, Bruce, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 21)
      - Coppola, Francis Ford, undated (Box 134, Folder 22)
      - Cornell, Joseph, 1976 (Box 134, Folder 23)
      - Coté, Guy, undated (Box 134, Folder 24)
      - D'Avino, Carmen, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 25)
      - Deren, Maya, undated (Box 134, Folder 26)
      - Duchamp, Marcel, 1948 (Box 134, Folder 27)
      - Fellini, Federico, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 28)
      - Fischinger, Oskar, 1949 (Box 134, Folder 29)
      - Forman, Milos, 1970s (Box 134, Folder 30)
      - Franju, Georges, 1949 (Box 134, Folder 31)
      - Frank, Robert, 1961 (Box 134, Folder 32)
      - Godard, Jean-Luc, 1966-1967 (Box 134, Folder 33)
      - Godfrey, [?], 1950s (Box 134, Folder 34)
      - Grede, Kjell, 1967-1969 (Box 134, Folder 35)
      - Herzog, Werner (and Amos Vogel), 1984, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 36)
      - Hitchcock, Alfred, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 37)
      - Janscó, Miklós, undated (Box 134, Folder 38)
      - Kaner, Sam, undated (Box 134, Folder 39)
      - Kirsanoff, Dimitri, 1927 (Box 134, Folder 40)
      - Kluver, [?], undated (Box 134, Folder 41)
      - Lee, Francis, 1948, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 42)
      - Luce, Ralph, 1948 (Box 134, Folder 43)
      - Lye, Len, undated (Box 134, Folder 44)
      - McClaren, Norman, undated (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Magritte, René, undated (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Makavejev, Dušan, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Malle, Louis, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Manuell, [George], 1930s-1940s (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Maysles, Albert and David, 1968 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Mekas, Jonas and Adolfas, 1964 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Myers, Richard, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Nicholson, Jack, 1970s (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Oshima, Nagisa, 1969-1970 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Pasolini, Pier Paolo, 1970s (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Peterson, Sidney, 1940s-1950s (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Putteman, Peter and [?], 1950s (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Resnais, Alain, 1966-1967 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - Roud, Richard (and Amos Vogel), 1950s (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - Schmid, David, undated (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - Schroeter, Werner, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 17)
      - Solanas, Fernardo, 1968 (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - Telberg, Val, undated (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - Vanderbeek, Stan, undated (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - Varda, Agnes and Others, 1950s (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - Vogel, Amos, 1938-1990s (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - Vogel, Amos and Marcia, 1955 March (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - Watkins, Peter, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 24)
      - Weegee, 1940s (Box 135, Folder 25)
      - Weiss, Peter, undated (Box 135, Folder 26)
      - Whitney, James and John, 1940s (Box 135, Folder 27)
      - Wildenhahn, Klaus, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 28)
      - Zilnick, Zelimir, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 29)
      - Zwartjes, Frans (and Cast), 1972 (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - Internationale Kurzfilmtage Oberhausen, 1962 (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Karlovy Vary Film Festival, 1960s, (2 Folders) (Box 135, Folder 32 to 33)
    - Negatives
      - Cinema 16, 1950s (Box 135, Folder 34)
      - "Poetry and the Film," 1953 October 28 (Box 135, Folder 35)
      - Vogel, Amos, 1930s, 1980s (Box 135, Folder 36)
    - New York Film Festival, 1960s (Box 135, Folder 37)
    - Very Important People Photographs, undated, 1950s-1970s (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV.2: Film Stills, 1920-1994
    This second subseries is composed primarily of photographs from films screened by Amos Vogel. Although there are stills from more "mainstream" films, the bulk of the films represented were independently produced. In many cases, these photographs may be the only surviving visual documentation of a particular production. The photographs are arranged alphabetically by film title and span Vogel's career. Some include accompanying material, such as publicity advertisements, negatives, and annotations written by Vogel for photographs that were used in his book Film as a Subversive Art.
    - Adebar, undated (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - The Adventures of Robinson Crusoe, 1953 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Agnus Dei, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Alptraum als Lebenslauf, undated (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - A Man with Three Coffins, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Ana, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Analogies, 1977 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Anamnesis, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - And the Fifth Horseman Is Fear, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Ariel, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Army of God, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Ashik Kerib, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - A Short Film about Killing, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - As You Desire Me, 1932 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Aus heiterem Himmel, undated (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - Awstrijskoje Polje, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1945 (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Behind Your Walls, undated (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Bei Namensnennung und im Zusammenhand mit der Viennela 1993 Abdruck honorarfrei, undated (Box 136, Folder 20)
    - Berlin Jerusalem, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 21)
    - Bicycle Thief, 1948 (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Biglal Ha-Milchama Hahi, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 23)
    - Blockade, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 24)
    - Black Peter, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 25)
    - Blanche, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 26)
    - Blood of the Beasts, 1949 (Box 136, Folder 27)
    - The Bomber Pilot, 1970 (Box 136, Folder 28)
    - Born in Flames, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - Bruxelles Transit, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - The Burmese Harp, 1956 (Box 136, Folder 31)
    - Busch Singt, 1935 (Box 136, Folder 32)
    - Cabinet of Dr. Caligari, 1920 (Box 136, Folder 33)
    - Canale Grande, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 34)
    - Cane Toads: An Unnatural History, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 35)
    - The Carabiniers, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 36)
    - Carnival of the Night, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 37)
    - Chan Is Missing, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 38)
    - Charmed Particles, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 39)
    - The Chelsea Girls, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 40)
    - Un Chien Andalou, 1929 (Box 136, Folder 41)
    - Chloe in the Afternoon, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 42)
    - The Columbus of Sex, 1970s (Box 136, Folder 43)
    - Commissar, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 44)
    - The Confrontation, 1969 (Box 136, Folder 45)
    - Couple/Regards/Positions, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 46)
    - The Cow, 1969 (Box 136, Folder 47)
    - Crumb, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 48)
    - Dear America, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - De Berg, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - The Deerhunter, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Delusions of Self-Immolation, undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Der Dibek, 1937 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Der schwarze Kasten, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Der Tunnel, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Les Deux Timides, 1928 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Diamonds of the Night, 1964 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Diary of a Country Priest, 1951 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Die blaue Distanz, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Documenteur, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Dogra Magra, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Don't Touch My Holocaust, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Door in the Wall, 1956 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - Double Suicide, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - Dreams That Money Can Buy, 1948 (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - Dyn Amo, 1972 (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - Eine Liebe wie andere auch, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - El, 1953 (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - Elegia, 1965 (Box 137, Folder 21)
    - Emak Bakia, 1927 (Box 137, Folder 22)
    - The End of August at Hotel Ozone, 1965 (Box 137, Folder 23)
    - Entracte, 1924 (Box 137, Folder 24)
    - Ernesto Che Guevara, das bolivanische Tagebuch, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 25)
    - ETC., undated (Box 137, Folder 26)
    - Family Viewing, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 27)
    - The Fiancés, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 28)
    - Film, 1965 (Box 137, Folder 29)
    - Film Two, undated (Box 137, Folder 30)
    - Fireworks, 1947 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Floating, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Flüstern und SCHREIEN, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Foules, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Friendship's Death, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Fuck Explosion MOD, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Gesucht: Monika Ertl, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Ghamis Zekwa/Nächtlicher Tanz, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Gimme Shelter, 1970 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Guns of the Trees, 1961 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Heaven and Earth Magic, 1962 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Heaven's Gate, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - The Henry Miller Odyssey, 1969 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Himmel und Erde, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 14)